hacres.com 2011-06-01

# Hallelujah Acres Privacy Policy

## We Respect Your Privacy

**Collection of Information**  
Hallelujah Acres does not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we don't require visitors to register or provide information to us in order to view our site. If you choose to register for Hallelujah Acres services, we will store your information in a secure area and use it for the sole purpose of providing the services you have requested. If you specifically agreed to follow-up contacts by us, or requested to be put on our mailing list, Hallelujah Acres may also contact you via email or regular mail from time to time. Under no circumstances will we use this information for anything not described in this privacy policy.

We will never sell or share your contact information with anyone outside of Hallelujah Acres.

If at anytime you wish to access, review and/or correct all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in the secure area you may request so. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows the error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to this information. You may also request to have your personal information removed from our databases at anytime.

Our site sometimes includes notices of sweepstakes or other promotions we are conducting, and we may permit you to enter electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (e.g., to contact you if you're a winner). We don't share this information you give us with anyone outside of Hallelujah Acres.

From time to time, our site may also be conducting questionnaires and surveys. Survey information is treated like all of the information we collect, and it is used to help us improve the appeal of our products and our site.

Hallelujah Acres takes your privacy and security seriously, for this reason we have established physical security measures including locked doors and files, electronic security and managerial controls that limit the potential for misuse of information by employees and contractors.

**Cookies**  
Like most companies, we may use "cookie" technology on our web site or sections of our website. When you log in, the cookie tells us whether you've visited us before or are a new visitor. The cookie doesn't track any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer. Cookies are simply the best way for us to be able to offer you the most enjoyable and hassle-free online experience.

**Questions / Concerns**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy and our website, please [contact us](http://www.hacres.com/contact).
